Guide to the Oliver C. Winston Papers ca. 1930-1973
Winston, Oliver C. Papers ca. 1930-1973
- Series V. Cornell University
  - Ithaca: the Plan for Downtown Ithaca, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Ithaca: maps, 1964, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Annual Report Cayuga County Planning Board, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Master Plan Background Study: Community Facilities Cayuga County Planning Board, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Master Plan Background Study: History Cayuga County Planning Board, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Master Plan Background Study: Physical Characteristics Cayuga County Planning Board, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Master Plan Background Study: Natural Resources Cayuga County Planning Board, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Master Plan Background Study: Analysis Cayuga County Planning Board, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Master Plan Background Study: Population & Economics Cayuga County Planning Board, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Development Proposals Cayuga County Planning Board (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Land Use & Transportation Plan Cayuga County Planning Board, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Auburn and Cayuga County, New York: A Reference Study (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Albert Meyer on Cayuga County and the City of Auburn Cayuga County Planning Board, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Central Area Plan, Auburn, New York (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - The Hector Land Use Area, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - A Summary Report of Suggested Development Patterns Chemung County Planning Board, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - County Development Plan: Elmira-Chemung County Metropolitan Area, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Land Use and Marketability Study: City of Elmira, New York, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - North-South Arterial Downtown Section: Elmira, New York, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - The Schuyler County Overall Economic Development Plan, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Binghamton: Ely Park Housing (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Annual Report Binghamton Urban Renewal Agency, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Schoharie??? Advance (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Welcome to Lake George (on advertising sign design and control) (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Comprehensive Plan, Town of Canandaigua, New York, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Comprehensive Plan, Town of Lyons, New York, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Master Plan, Town of Phelps, New York, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Lysander New Community: Plan Digest, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - MDA Report: Status of Expressway Program in Onondaga County, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - A Proposed Plan for the Development of Oneida County, New York, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - A Community Renewal Program, Syracuse, New York (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - A Regional Planning and Development Board for Central New York, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Annual Report Central New York Finger Lakes Regional Planning and Development Board, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - A Plan for the Development of the Town of Cortlandville, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - The New York State Canal System, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Program for Cooperative Study for Comprehensive Water Resources Development of the Cayuga Lake Basin, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Program for Cooperative Study for Comprehensive Water Resources Development of the Eastern Oswego River Basin, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Planning the City of Socialist Man Jack C. Fisher (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Universities and Cities Kermit C. Parsons (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Control of Urban Land Subdivision John W. Reps, Jerry L. Smith (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - The Tidewater Colonies John W. Reps (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Selected Papers on Operational Gaming Allan G. Feldt, ed. (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - State Planning: a Bibliography of Selected Items Henry P. Henderson (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - The New Building Block, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - The Future of American Planning John W. Reps, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Operational Gaming in Planning and Architecture Allan G. Feldt, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - The Role of Support in the Growth of Planning Education in the United States Kermit C. Parsons, Barclay G. Jones, Courtney Riordan, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - The Future of Central City Organization of Cornell University Planners (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Planning the Future Residential Environment Organization of Cornell University Planners, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Community Directions and Alternatives John L. Gann, Jr. (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Alternatives for Planning in Small Communities John L. Gann, Jr., 1970 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Soils Inventory for the Development of the Caroline Ski Hill Area Gerald W. Olson, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Soil Survey, Tompkins County, New York, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Soil Survey of Cornell University Property and Adjacent Areas, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Maintaining Viable Farming in Areas of Urban Expansion Cornell University Department of Agricultural Economics, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 4-6)
  - The Role of the Cooperative Extension Service in New York State's Changing and Adjusting Agriculture, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - The Nature and Distribution of Farming in New York State Howard E. Conklin, Robert E. Linton, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - A Survey of Land Owners Related to the Rural Development Program, Broome County, New York Bruce T. Wilkins, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Ecology of Cayuga Lake and the Proposed Bell Station Cornell University Water Resources & Marine Sciences Center, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Ecology of Cayuga Lake and the Proposed Bell Station: Summary Cornell University Water Resources & Marine Sciences Center, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Service to New York State: Summary Report 1965-69 Cornell University Water Resources & Marine Sciences Center, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Impact of Water Based Recreation: A Proposal Cornell University Water Resources Center (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Farm Research v.30, no.2, June 1964 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Report on Water Resources: Pt. 1 Genesee County Resources Development Committee, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Opportunities for Rural Resource Development: Joint Pennsylvania-New York State Proposal for Appalachian Region (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Nonfarm People in the Open Country: Tompkins County, New York Charles Holt, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Promise of New York's Rural Resources New York State College of Agriculture (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - New York's Development and One Man, One Vote. Comprehensive Regional Development. Planning and Perception of Needs in Five Upstate New York Counties New York State College of Agriculture, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Operation Advance Fact Sheet Kit / New York State Colleges of Agriculture and Home Economics (Box 22, Folder 10-12)
  - Managing Community Growth New York State Cooperative Extension (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Extension's Role in Education for Living New York State Cooperative Extension, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Extension Education and Related Research in Citizen Management of Community Resources New York State Cooperative Extension, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Land, Water, People, and Economic Growth New York State Cooperative Extension, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Economic Indicators: Ithaca, Tompkins County A.M. Hillhouse, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - The People of Schuyler County, New York Cornell University Department of Rural Sociology, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - A Social Analysis of Southold Town, Long Island Robert L. Carroll, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Metrotran-2000 Robert A. Wolf, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Plan for the Central Business District of Baltimore, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Charles Center: a Beginning (newspaper clippings), 1958-1959 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Downtown Binghamton, New York, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Broome County 1980, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Midtown Plaza, Rochester (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Ithaca Urban Area, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 6)